corporatetrainingmaterials.com 2016-12-19

# What information do we collect?

What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, or subscribe to our
newsletter.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail
address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site
anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To improve customer service: Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer
service requests and support needs
To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged,
transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other
than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To send periodic emails: The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send
you information and updates pertaining to your order. You may unsubscribe at any time.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when
you place an order.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure
Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those
authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information
confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our
business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may
also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce
our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

Canada's Anti-Spam Legislation
We abide by the CASL rules and regulations. When you sign up for our courseware samples, you may
unsubscribe from our list at any time. For more information on this law, please visit:
http://fightspam.gc.ca/eic/site/030.nsf/eng/h_00039.html#
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the
California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to
outside parties without your consent.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do
not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are
all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy. Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to
change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
https://corporatetrainingmaterials.com/pages/contact
116 Provost Street
New Glasgow, NS Canada
B2H 2P4
Telephone: 902-695-3660
Fax: 902-695-3661
This policy is powered by Trust Guard, the place for website security scans
